[Alexey Obukhov]

[004917641032303]

[alexey.obukhov@hotmail.com]

Summary: I am a creative and innovative IT Engineer with a passion for developing new ideas and concepts. I have been working in the field of IT since my school days and have gained significant experience in automatisation, application development, and data analysis. As an IT Engineer, I am currently leading a department focused on developing applications for testing semiconductors.

Experience:

IT Engineer Racyics Nov 2021 – Present (1 yr 5 mos)

- Develop and maintain automatisation tools
- Design and develop applications for testing semiconductors
- Analyze and visualize data using Python (Matplotlib + Pandas mostly)

Software Tester [Joynext] Feb 2020 – Jan 2021 (1 yr)

- Automated testing of navigation software
- Identified and reported software defects
- Worked collaboratively with development teams to ensure timely bug fixes

Software Tester [Joynext] Dec 2017 – Aug 2019 (1 yr 9 mos)

- Conducted manual testing of navigation software
- Analyzed software defects and reported them to the development team
- Worked with cross-functional teams to ensure software quality

Student Assistant Hochschule für Technik und Wirtschaft Oct 2015 – Aug 2016 (11 mos)

- Programmed C-applications for Opal-learning-project GRIPSS
- Conducted research on computer science topics
- Assisted professors with various administrative tasks

Education:

 $\begin{tabular}{ll} Hochschule f \ddot{u}r Technik und Wirtschaft Geomatics, \\ 2017-Aug~2022 \end{tabular}$

TU Dublin College of Engineering & Built Environment, Exchange semester Sep 2019 – Feb 2020

Hochschule für Technik und Wirtschaft Applied Informatics and Mathematics, Sep $2015 - \text{Aug}\ 2016$

Saint Petersburg State University Applied Mathematics and Informatics, $2007-2011\,$

Skills:

- Programming languages: Python, C, Java, SQL
- Software development tools: Visual Studio, Eclipse, JIRA
- Data analysis and visualization: NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib
- Agile development methodologies